Guide to the National Education Association-Special Collections records, 1857-2015 NEA1007.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Programs, 1930-2000; Series 7; 19.5 Linear Feet
  - Program Budgets, 1973-1978; Series 7 (Box 3684, Folder 6)
  - Putting Education on Display, 1964; Series 7 (Box 4054, Folder 6)
  - Read Across America Day; Proclamation by President Obama, 2011; Series 7 (Box 5079, Folder 3)
  - The Student NEA Looks at Accreditation, July 1975; Series 7 (Box 4904, Folder 4)
  - Teacher Centers and Needs Assessment, 1980; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 21)
  - Teacher Centers and Secondary Teachers, 1980; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 22)
  - Teacher Day USA Kit, May 9, 1984, Series 7 (Box 4424, Folder 7)
  - Teacher Day USA Kit, 1985; Series 7 (Box 4424, Folder 8)
  - Teacher - Designed Population Education, April 1976; Series 7 (Box 4904, Folder 3)
  - Teacher-Parent Relationship, 1985; Series 7 (Box 4074, Folder 4)
  - Teacher to Teacher Communications: Report of the NEA's Pan-Pacific Satellite Experiment - 1976, Series 7 (Box 4093, Folder 15)
  - The Newspaper in the Classroom, 1985; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 7)
  - The Role of High-Stakes Testing in School Reform, 1993; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 14)
  - Training Program-Building High Performance Teams-Michigan Education Association [file 1/2], ca. 1987; Series 7 (Box 2801, Folder 3)
  - Training Program-Building High Performance Teams-Michigan Education Association [file 2/2], ca. 1987; Series 7 (Box 2801, Folder 4)
  - Training Program-The Faculty Representative: A Promoter and Maintainer of Membership, 1979; Series 7 (Box 2801, Folder 5)
    Negatives have been removed from this folder.
  - Training Program-Issues Organizing: A Training Program for Local Association Presidents [file 1/3], 1976; Series 7 (Box 2801, Folder 6)
  - Training Program-Issues Organizing: A Training Program for Local Association Presidents [file 2/3], 1976; Series 7 (Box 2801, Folder 7)
  - Training Program-Issues Organizing: A Training Program for Local Association Presidents [file 3/3], 1976; Series 7 (Box 2801, Folder 8)
  - Training Program-Koffee Klatch Trainers Manual, 1981; Series 7 (Box 2802, Folder 1)
    Contains two reel-to-reel audiocassettes, "Koffee Klatch Episode 1 and 2" and "Koffee Klatch Episode 3 and 4"
  - Training Program-Pre-Arbitration Grievance Processing, A Training Program for Grievance Representatives, 1979; Series 7 (Box 2802, Folder 2)
  - Training Program-Program Development: A Training Program for Local Association Presidents, 1977; Series 7 (Box 2802, Folder 3)
  - Training Program-Site-Based Decisionmaking: A Guidance and Training Manual [file 1/3], ca. 1975; Series 7 (Box 2802, Folder 4)
  - Training Program-Site-Based Decisionmaking: A Guidance and Training Manual [file 2/3], ca. 1975; Series 7 (Box 2802, Folder 5)
  - Training Program-Site-based Decisionmaking: A Guidance and Training Manual [file 3/3], ca. 1975; Series 7 (Box 2803, Folder 1)
  - Training Program-The Vital Link: A Training Program for Local Association Leaders: Trainers Manual, 1980; Series 7 (Box 2803, Folder 2)
  - Two Million Heroes: A One-Act Teaching Career Month Play for Jr. and Sr. High School Students, 1965; Series 7 (Box 4054, Folder 7)
  - Quality Teaching: Questions every State Policy Maker Ought to Ask, 1986; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 10)
  - Reading: Trends and Challenge, 1981; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 11)
  - Ready Schools, February 1998; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 12)
  - Remedial Reading, 1990; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 13)
  - Sexual Harassment in Higher Education: concepts and Issues, 1992; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 15)
  - Student Suicide: A Guide for Intervention, 1989; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 16)
  - Survey of 1993 State Legislation Affecting Teacher Retirement, 1994; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 17)
  - Survey of 1994 State Legislation Affecting Teacher and Educational Support Personnel Retirement, 1995; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 18)
  - Survey of 1995 State Legislation Affecting Teacher and Educational Support Personnel Retirement, Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 19)
  - Vocabulary Knowledge: Guidelines for Instruction, 1990; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 23)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Manuals-"Campaign to Win" and "WLTP Overview", ca. 1979; Series 7 (Box 2804, Folder 1)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-"Personal Assessment of Leadership Skills", ca. 1980; Series 7 (Box 2804, Folder 2)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-"Personal Assessment of Leadership Skills" [file 1/2], ca. 1980; Series 7 (Box 2804, Folder 3)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-"Personal Assessment of Leadership Skills" [file 2/2], ca. 1980; Series 7 (Box 2804, Folder 4)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Program Overview-Draft, ca. 1979; Series 7 (Box 2804, Folder 5)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Trainer's Manual-"Group Process Skills", 1982-1984; Series 7 (Box 2804, Folder 6)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Trainer's Manual-"Group Process Manual" Level II, Module 2, 1982; Series 7 (Box 2805, Folder 1)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Trainer's Manual-"Group Process Skills", 1982-1986; Series 7 (Box 2805, Folder 2)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Trainer's Manual-"Personal Leadership Skills" [file 1/2], 1980; Series 7 (Box 2805, Folder 3)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Trainer's Manual-"Personal Leadership Skills" [file 2/2], 1980; Series 7 (Box 2805, Folder 4)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Trainer's Manual-"Organizational Analysis Skills" [file 1/2], 1988; Series 7 (Box 2805, Folder 5)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Trainer's Manual-"Organizational Analysis Skills" [file 2/2], 1988; Series 7 (Box 2805, Folder 6)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Trainer's Manual-"Organizational Analysis Skills", 1988; Series 7 (Box 2806, Folder 1)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Trainer's Manual-"Personal Leadership Skills", 1980-1989; Series 7 (Box 2806, Folder 2)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Trainer's Manual-"Personal Leadership Skills", 1980-1989; Series 7 (Box 2806, Folder 3)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Trainer's Resource Maerials, ca. 1980; Series 7 (Box 2806, Folder 4)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Training Manual-The Second Year [file 1/3], 1977-1978; Series 7 (Box 2806, Folder 5)
    Audiocassette tape, "I Am Woman," copyright 1972 Capitol Records Inc.
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Training Manual-The Second Year [file 2/3], 1977-1978; Series 7 (Box 2806, Folder 6)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Training Manual-The Second Year [file 3/3], 1977-1978; Series 7 (Box 2807, Folder 1)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Training Workshop-"Sexual Harassment in Your Workplace", ca. 1980; Series 7 (Box 2807, Folder 2)
  - Women's Leadership Training Program-Workbook-"Campaigning to Win: Helping Women Win Association Office", ca. 1980; Series 7 (Box 2807, Folder 3)
- Projects, 1953-2000; Series 8; 90 Linear Feet
  Series: Arranged alphabetically by Project name, the alphabetically by file title and finally chronologically within each file.
  Biographical/Historical note
  The NEA appropriated funds to assist discernible segments of members in situations involving the implementation of innovative ideas. The purpose of this policy was to provide a systematic procedure for adminstering project funds. In order to meet the criteria for financial support, the project had to: assist the priorties of the NEA; be achievable within a manageable amount of time; and have a built-in evaluation system as part of its design. Special consideration was given to projects which test new ideas or concepts or provide new approaches to old problems, as well as to projects with financial commitments outside of the NEA budget.
  For more detailed backgrounds on the projects in this series, see the NEA Handbook, published annually.
  Source: NEA Handbook 1974-75
  Series contains materials created as part of projects sponsored by the NEA or the NEA Foundation. The projects were often worked by or in partnership with other institutions, including member affiliates, unaffiliated education associations such as the Asociacion de Maestros de Puerto Rico, government agencies, universities,student groups, community groups and private companies such as IBM and the Carnegie Corporation. A number of different projects are included in the series. The prominent projects included in this series include campaigns to: push for federal tax and resource allocation reform, create a Department of Education, assess and restructure the NEA national headquarters, design an early NEA website, integrate technology into education, standardize job descriptions for educators, erect affordable housing for educators and retired educators, show the comparable inequity of educator salaries to similar careers, lower the voting age, and studies of crime and violence among student-age populations.
  These projects cover a variety of topics, some of which are go beyond education, providing great insight into the NEA's work in diverse areas of American public life, including legislative and judicial campaigns on behalf of both educators and students as well as the changes brought to both the organization and to educators in general by technological changes of the late 20th century.
  The files include action plans, affiliate histories, agendas, brochures, comic books, correspondence, 5 ¼ inch floppy disks, housing blueprints, marketing products, memos, minutes, pamphlets, project strategies, proposals, reports and surveys.
  Some materials were separated for size. Referral forms in the files provide information on where the oversize material can be found.
  - Academically Talented Student, 1959-1960; Series 8 (Box 2606, Folder 1)
  - 1999-2000 Projects [1/3], Series 8 (Box 4655, Folder 4)
  - 1999-2000 Projects [2/3], Series 8 (Box 4655, Folder 5)
  - 1999-2000 Projects [3/3], Series 8 (Box 4655, Folder 6)
  - 2000-2001 Projects [1/2], Series 8 (Box 4655, Folder 7)
  - 2000-2001 Projects [2/2], Series 8 (Box 4655, Folder 8)
  - Academically Talented Student-Brochure, ca. 1958; Series 8 (Box 2606, Folder 2)
  - Academically Talented Student-Conference-Washington, D.C., 6-8 February 1958; Series 8 (Box 2606, Folder 3)
  - Academically Talented Student-"Methods of Identification-The Complexity of the Problem", ca. 1958; Series 8 (Box 2606, Folder 4)
  - Academically Talented Student-Packet, 1962; Series 8 (Box 2606, Folder 5)
  - The Academically Talented Student Pamphlets, undated; series 8 (Box 4398, Folder 22)
  - Academically Talented Student-Publication-"The Gifted Child Quarterly", Winter 1975; Series 8 (Box 2606, Folder 6)
  - Academically Talented Student-"A Report on Recent Research in the Field of the Academically Talented", October 1958; Series 8 (Box 2606, Folder 7)
  - Alaska [Grant Proposal], 1999-2003; Series 8 (Box 3173, Folder 1)
  - Alaska Pay Equity Cadre, 1999-2000; Series 8 (Box 3173, Folder 2)
  - The American Cities Project-"A Report on the Plight and Promise of America's Urban Centers", September 1992; Series 8 (Box 2606, Folder 8)
  - The American Cities Project-"A Report on the Plight and Promise of America's Urban Centers"-Appendices, September 1992; Series 8 (Box 2606, Folder 9)
  - Bell Multicultural High School, August 22, 1990; Series 8 (Box 4895, Folder 8)
  - Bibliography on New Media and Instructional Technology, February 1962; series 8 (Box 4344, Folder 13)
  - Camille Relief Project-Assistance, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2606, Folder 10)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Coalition for Democratic Values, 1990; Series 8 (Box 2607, Folder 1)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Community Forum, 1992-1993; Series 8 (Box 2607, Folder 2)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Defense Spending under the Clinton Administration, 1994-1995; Series 8 (Box 2607, Folder 3)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Defense Spending under the Clinton Administration, 1993-1995; Series 8 (Box 2607, Folder 4)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Defense Spending under the Clinton Administration, 1991-1994; Series 8 (Box 2607, Folder 5)
    Contains 19 color slides.
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Economic Competitiveness and the Human Capital Investment Gap, 1991-1992; Series 8 (Box 2607, Folder 6)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Local Points, 1992; Series 8 (Box 2607, Folder 7)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Loose Items in Box, 1988-1991; Series 8 (Box 2607, Folder 8)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Loose Items in Box, 1991; Series 8 (Box 2608, Folder 1)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Loose Items in Box, 1990-1996; Series 8 (Box 2608, Folder 2)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Loose Items in Box, 1992-1994; Series 8 (Box 2608, Folder 3)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Loose Items in Box, 1988-1990; Series 8 (Box 2608, Folder 4)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Mailing Report, 1993; Series 8 (Box 2608, Folder 5)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Mr. Sam Pizzigatti, NEA Publishing, 1990-2000; Series 8 (Box 2608, Folder 6)
    Pizzigatti, Sam
  - Campaign for New Priorities-NEA Governance, 1990-1991; Series 8 (Box 2608, Folder 7)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-NEA Materials, 1990-1991; Series 8 (Box 2608, Folder 8)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-NEA Workshop, 1989-1992; Series 8 (Box 2609, Folder 1)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-PRISEE, 1992-1993; Series 8 (Box 2609, Folder 2)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-A-E [file 1/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2609, Folder 3)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-A-E [file 2/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2609, Folder 4)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-A-E [file 3/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2609, Folder 5)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-F-J [file 1/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2610, Folder 1)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-F-J [file 2/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2610, Folder 2)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-F-J [file 3/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2610, Folder 3)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-K-M [file 1/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2610, Folder 4)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-K-M [file 2/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2610, Folder 5)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-K-M [file 3/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2610, Folder 6)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-N-P [file 1/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2611, Folder 1)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-N-P [file 2/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2611, Folder 2)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-N-P [file 3/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2611, Folder 3)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-Q-T [file 1/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2611, Folder 4)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-Q-T [file 2/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2612, Folder 1)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-Q-T [file 3/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2612, Folder 2)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-U-Z [file 1/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2612, Folder 3)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-U-Z [file 2/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2612, Folder 4)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Proclamations-U-Z [file 3/3], 1992; Series 8 (Box 2612, Folder 5)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Resolution Campaign, 1992-1993; Series 8 (Box 2612, Folder 6)
  - Campaign for New Priorities-Talks, ca. 1992; Series 8 (Box 2612, Folder 7)
  - A Compilation of Material on Instructional Technology and the NEA Technological Development Project, ca. 1962; series 8 (Box 4344, Folder 14)
  - Co-Op Project-Georgia, 1995-1996; Series 8 (Box 2613, Folder 1)
  - Co-Op Project-Georgia, 1996; Series 8 (Box 2613, Folder 2)
  - Co-Op Project-Georgia Association of Educators, 1996-1998; Series 8 (Box 2613, Folder 3)
  - Co-Op Project-Georgia Association of Educators, 1994-1997; Series 8 (Box 2613, Folder 4)
  - Co-Op Project-Georgia Association of Educators, 1995-1997; Series 8 (Box 2613, Folder 5)
  - Co-Op Project-Texas, 1986-2000; Series 8 (Box 2614, Folder 1)
  - Co-Op Project-Texas, 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 2614, Folder 2)
  - Co-Op Project-Texas, 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 2614, Folder 3)
  - Co-Op Project-Texas, 1987-2000; Series 8 (Box 2614, Folder 4)
  - Co-Op Project-Utah, 1987-1999; Series 8 (Box 2615, Folder 1)
  - Co-Op Project-Utah, 1996-1999; Series 8 (Box 2615, Folder 2)
  - Co-Op Project-Wyoming, 1988-1999; Series 8 (Box 2615, Folder 3)
  - Co-Op Project-Wyoming, 1991-1998; Series 8 (Box 2615, Folder 4)
  - Department of Education Week, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 1)
  - Department of Education Week-Ad Hoc Committee, Noted Entertainer, 1971 February 18; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 2)
  - Department of Education Week-Addendum Cabinet Post, ca. 1971; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 3)
  - Department of Education Week-Addendum-Rationale, ca. 1971; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 4)
  - Department of Education Week-Adm. Bill-Human Resources, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 5)
  - Department of Education Week-American Defense Education Act, 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 6)
  - Department of Education Week-American Defense Education Act, 1982-1985; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 7)
  - Department of Education Week-American Defense Education Act, 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 8)
  - Department of Education Week-American Defense Education Act Background Material, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 9)
  - Department of Education Week-American Defense Education Act Hearing-Senate, 1985 July; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 10)
  - Department of Education Week-American Defense Education Act Fact Sheet, 1984; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 11)
  - Department of Education Week-American Defense Education Act-House Subcommittee Material, 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 12)
  - Department of Education Week-American Defense Education Act Proposals, 1985; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 13)
  - Department of Education Week-American Defense Education Act-State Correspondence, 1982-1983; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 14)
  - Department of Education Week-ADEA Statistics/Related Data, 1983; Series 8 (Box 2616, Folder 15)
  - Department of Education Week-Announcement Letter, Actual Follow-up Letter, 1971 February-March; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 1)
  - Department of Education Week-Ash Report (Reorganization), 1971 February; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 2)
  - Department of Education Week-Bain, Helen-August, 1971 and Future, 1971 August 13; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 3)
    Pate-Bain, Helen
  - Department of Education Week-Big 6, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 4)
  - Department of Education Week-Bill (Sample), 1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 6)
  - Department of Education Week-Board of Directors, 1971 July; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 7)
  - Department of Education Week-Board of Directors, Executive Committee, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 8)
  - Department of Education Week-Board of Directors-February 24, 25, 26, 1971 February 24-26; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 9)
  - Department of Education Week-Brochure, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 11)
  - Department of Education Week-Briefing Confirmations, 1971 February-March; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 12)
  - Department of Education Week-Budget, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 13)
  - Department of Education Week-Cabinet Commitment Memos, 1971 February; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 14)
  - Department of Education Week-Cabinet level, Congressional members contacted, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 15)
  - Department of Education Week-Cabinet Meeting 2-4-71, 1974 February 4; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 16)
  - Department of Education Week-Calendar-Time Schedule, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 17)
  - Department of Education Week-Cartoon Posters, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 18)
  - Department of Education Week-Clippings, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 19)
  - Department of Education Week-Coalition, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 20)
  - Department of Education Week-Colortone, 1971 March; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 21)
  - Department of Education Week-Commitment Forms, NCSEA, Feb. 15, 16 1971, Mayflower Hotel, 1971 February 15-16; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 22)
  - Department of Education Week-Commitment letters from States, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 23)
  - Department of Education Week-Congress of Parents and Teachers-1971, 1971 May; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 24)
  - Department of Education Week-Congressional Contact Forms, 1971 February; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 25)
  - Department of Education Week-Congressional Contact Report Forms (visits), 1971 March; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 26)
  - Department of Education Week-Congressional Record Edmundson-Oklahoma, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 27)
  - Department of Education Week-Congressional Roster Progress Report June, 1971, 1971 March-June; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 28)
  - Department of Education Week-Congressmen Visited, 1971 March; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 29)
  - Department of Education Week-Contact Roster UAED, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2617, Folder 30)
  - Department of Education Week-Contacts (supplemental), ca. 1971; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 1)
  - Department of Education Week-Correspondence (general), 1971-1972; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 2)
  - Department of Education Week-Department of Human Resources S-1432, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 3)
  - Department of Education Week-Government Operations Committee, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 4)
  - Department of Education Week-Government Operations Subcommittee, 1972; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 5)
  - Department of Education Week-Government Operations, H.R. 5609, 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 6)
  - Department of Education Week-Graphics, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 7)
  - Department of Education Week-GRIP Conference, ca. 1971; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 8)
  - Department of Education Week-Hearings on American Defense Education Act H.R. 881 10/26/83, 1983 October; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 9)
  - Department of Education Week-H.R. 881 American Defense Education Act, 1983; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 10)
  - Department of Education Week-H.R. 881-Perkins ADEA, 1983; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 11)
  - Department of Education Week-H.R. 1310 Working Papers, 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 12)
  - Department of Education Week-H.R. 2840 Legal Counsel Bill Summaries, 1985; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 13)
  - Department of Education Week-H.R. 5609 May 15, 1984, 1984 May; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 14)
  - Department of Education Week-Info Packets to Lobbyists, ADEA Senate Contacts April '85, 1984-1985; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 15)
  - Department of Education Week-Informational Program, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 16)
  - Department of Education Week-Iowa, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 17)
  - Department of Education Week-Legislative Commission Actions, Executive Commission, Board of Directors, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 18)
  - Department of Education Week-Lobby Contacts w/Ms. Bain 11-21-71 and later, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 19)
  - Department of Education Week-Loose Items in Box, 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 2618, Folder 20)
  - Department of Education Week-Mailing Numbers by States, ca. 1971; Series 8 (Box 2619, Folder 1)
  - Department of Education Week-Marland Letter, 1971 July 12; Series 8 (Box 2619, Folder 2)
  - Department of Education Week-Material Packets, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2619, Folder 3)
  - Department of Education Week-Materials Sent To States, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2619, Folder 4)
  - Department of Education Week-Memos, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2619, Folder 5)
  - Department of Education Week-Memo to President Bain-Compedium, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2619, Folder 6)
  - Department of Education Week-Memoranda, Helen Bain, 1971 March-April; Series 8 (Box 2619, Folder 7)
  - Department of Education Week-National Defense Education Act, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2619, Folder 8)
  - Department of Education Week-National Party Platform, 1971 May 19; Series 8 (Box 2619, Folder 9)